新月
這些狂暴的歡愉往往也終於狂暴
" These violent delights have violent ends,
最是那輝煌的幻滅 如火親吻火藥
"and in their triumph die, like fire and powder,
隨吻即逝
"which, as they kiss, consume."
奶奶?
Gran?
Edward 別 她會看見你的
Edward, don't! She'll see you.
好吧
Okay.
Gran 我給你介紹一下...
Gran, I'd like you to meet...
生日快樂 Bella
Happy birthday, Bella.
生日快樂
Happy birthday.
我們不是說好了不送禮物的嗎?
I thought we agreed, no presents.
我的這份沒有包裝 所以不算
Well, the one from me's not wrapped, so it doesn't count.
我很喜歡 謝謝 老爸
That's actually great. Thanks, Dad.
這個是你媽媽送你的 我們協調過的
It goes with this one from your mom. We coordinated.
嗯 她協調的我
Well, she coordinated me.
你可以用來放四年級的照片
It's to put your pictures in from senior year.
四年級了啊
Senior year.
- 你怎麼一下子變老太婆了? - 我沒有 還沒那麼老呢
- How'd you get so old so fast? - I didn't. It's not that old.
不知道 那是一根白頭髮嗎?
I don't know. Is that a gray hair?
不可能
No. No way.
生日快樂
Happy birthday.
哈哈哈 真好笑
That's really funny.
第三名失蹤的遠足者被認定死亡
Another missing hiker brings the total to three presumed dead.
護林員正在搜尋傷人的動物...
Rangers are searching for the killer animal...
* Situation's all critical *
Situation's all critical
* You've got to look first before you go *
You've got to look first before you go
是Bella Bella!
It's Bella. Bella!
- 早 - 我...
- Hi. - I'm...
今天是大日子啊 Bella
Today's the big day, Bella.
"羅密歐與朱麗葉"論文截止日期
R and J essay due.
- 哦 是的 - 汝在何處 Bella?
- Oh, yeah. - Wherefore art thou, Bella?
我想給你們拍張照片 我媽想讓我收集起來
Let me take a picture of you guys. My mom wants me to put together, like,
弄成個盛滿記憶的剪貼簿
a scrapbook full of memories.
- 哦 - 當然 來吧
- Oh. - Cool. Yeah.
我拍吧 我不上相
I take them. I'm not in them.
- 別別 過來 - 今天你得一起照
- No, no, no, come here. - Well, you are today.
如果我鼻子被照的很大的話 你得給我PS一下 好吧?
You'll photoshop this if my nose looks big, right?
別擔心 相片裡有我吶 就沒人看你們了
Don't worry, I'm in the picture. No one will be looking at you guys.
很好
That's good.
好了 Cullen來了
Oh, good. Cullen's here.
回聊
Well, talk to you later.
- 生日快樂 - 別提這個
- Happy birthday. - Don't remind me.
嗯
Mmm.
Bella 你的生日是絕對要慶祝的
Bella, your birth is definitely something to celebrate.
- 是啊 但是別慶祝我變老 - 變老?
- Yeah, but my aging's not. - Your aging?
我覺著18歲就擔心這事兒 有點過早了
I think 18 is a little young to start worrying about that.
我比你老一歲了
It's one year older than you.
不是的 我109歲了
No, it isn't. I'm 109.
那麼 或許我不該交這麼老的男朋友
Well, maybe I shouldn't be dating such an old man.
- 嗯 - 那太惡了 我應該深惡痛絕才是
- Mmm. - It's gross. I should be thoroughly repulsed.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
- 我們得上課去了 - 好吧
- We have to go to class. - Okay.
等一下
Wait a second.
有人找你
Someone wants you.
- Bella! - Jacob!
怎麼?
What?
你們先聊
I'll leave you to talk.
你好哇 肌肉男 你知道嗎 合成類固醇對你有害
Hello, biceps! You know, anabolic steroids are really bad for you.
我只是長大了而已 Bella
Well, I'm just filling out, Bella.
如果咱常在一起玩的話 你就不會這麼驚訝了
You know, it wouldn't seem so drastic if we hung out more.
你轉學算了 你可以和白人們一起玩
You should switch schools. You can come hang out with the palefaces.
不必了 我更傾向於寄宿學校的排他性
I'm all right. I prefer the rez school's exclusivity.
專收印第安原住民的學校
這裡什麼爛人都收
They let any old riffraff into this place.
- 明白了 那你為何大駕光臨呢? - 嗯
- I see. Then why are you slumming it? - Mmm-hmm.
我只是過來給愛車買配件
I was just buying a part for the Rabbit.
等弄好了你真該過來試一下
You should really come take a ride when it's done.
跑的快嗎?
Is it fast?
嗯
Um.
還好吧
It's decent.
- 我開玩笑呢 - 好吧 不錯
- I'm kidding. - Okay. Good.
嘿 生日快樂
Hey, happy birthday.
你老爸跟我老爸說了 所以...
Your dad told my dad, so...
是啊 他不說才怪
Yeah, of course he did.
有一天我看到這個 然後我想起你了
I saw this the other day and thought of you.
除惡夢噠
Catches bad dreams.
我正缺這個呢
That's kind of perfect.
謝謝
Thank you.
不客氣
No problem.
- 見到你很高興 - 是啊 回頭再見
- Good seeing you. - Yeah, I'll see you later.
再見
Bye.
憑啥Jacob Black能送你禮物 而我卻不能?
So how come Jacob Black gets to give you a gift and I don't?
因為我沒有可以回贈你的東西
Because I have nothing to give back to you.
Bella 你的一呼一吸 就給了我全世界
Bella, you give me everything just by breathing.
看到了沒? 謝謝
See? Thank you.
- 我別無他求了 - Bella!
- That's all I want. - Bella!
- 生日快樂! - 噓!
- Happy birthday! - Shh, shh!
我記得我說過不要禮物的
I thought I said no presents.
我已經預見你打開它了 你猜怎麼著
I've already seen you open it, and guess what,
你特喜歡它
you love it.
今晚穿上它來我們家
You're gonna wear it tonight. Our place.
拜託了 好不? 肯定有意思
Come on. Please? It'll be fun.
- 好吧 - 太棒了!
- Okay. All right. - Great!
7點見
Okay, I'll see you at 7:00.
Jasper 又控制我的情緒 太不公平了
Jasper, no fair with the mood control thing.
不好意思 Bella 生日...
Sorry, Bella. Happy...
算了
Never mind.
相信我 你不能相信吸血鬼
You can't trust vampires. Trust me.
噢我的愛! 我的妻子!
O my love! My wife!
死神雖然吸幹了你甜蜜的氣息
Death, that hath sucked the honey of thy breath
卻沒有力量摧毀你的美麗
hath had no power yet upon thy beauty.
你沒有被征服
Thou art not conquered.
美麗的紅旗仍然輕拂著你的嘴唇和面頰
Beauty's ensign yet is crimson in thy lips and in thy cheeks.
死神的白旗還未插到那裡
And death's pale flag is not advanced there.
我討厭慶祝生日
I hate being celebrated.
有人比你慘多了 你看羅密歐
There are worse tragedies. I mean, look at Romeo.
因自己純犯傻行為 害死了他的真愛
Killed his true love out of sheer stupidity.
是啊
Yeah.
然而有一件事我嫉妒他
Though I do envy him one thing.
朱麗葉太完美了
Juliet is, like, perfect.
如果你喜歡那種超級完美的話
If you like that obviously beautiful sort of thing.
不是指她 我意思是自殺
Not the girl, the suicide.
幾乎不可能...
It's nearly impossible for...
對某些人來說
For some people.
人類的話 一點毒藥
For humans, a little poison,
心臟上插一刀
a dagger to the heart.
有很多不同的選擇
There's so many different options.
你為什麼這麼說?
Why would you say that?
因為我曾考慮過一次
Because I had to consider it once.
我當時不知道能否及時救你
I didn't know if I'd get to you in time.
我得有個類似的準備
I had to come up with some kind of plan.
什麼準備?
What was the plan?
就是我會去意大利去惹Volturi家族
That I'd go to Italy and provoke the Volturi.
- 什麼家族? - Volturi
- The what? - The Volturi.
現在 有誰能重複一下 最後幾行的抑揚格五音步
Now, who'd like to repeat the last few lines of iambic pentameter
來證明剛才認真聽了?
just to show they were paying attention?
Cullen先生?
Mr. Cullen?
好的 Berty先生
Yes, Mr. Berty.
啊 我要在這兒永遠安息
"O here will I set up my everlasting rest
從我這厭惡人生的軀體上 掙脫厄運的奴役
"and shake the yoke of inauspicious stars from this world-wearied flesh.
眼睛 最後再看一次
"Eyes, look your last.
手臂 最後擁抱一次吧!
"Arms, take your last embrace!
在你的雙唇呼吸之處
"And, lips, O you, the doors of breath,
印下堂堂正正的一吻 與死神簽下永世的契約!
"seal with a righteous kiss a dateless bargain to engrossing death!"
大家要注意看屏幕
Eyes on the screen, people.
我就這樣在這一吻中死去
ROMEO: Thus with a kiss I die.
Volturi家族淵源悠久 能力強大
The Volturi are a very old, very powerful family.
我猜他們是我們這類中 最接近皇家血統的了
I guess they're the closest thing to royalty my world has.
- 那個是Carlisle嗎? - 是的
- Is that Carlisle? - Yeah.
他與他們一起住過幾十年
He lived with them for a few decades.
他說他們非常文雅 當然 不尊重人類的生命
Described them as very refined. No respect for human life, of course,
但是至少尊重藝術和科學
but a respect for the arts and the sciences, at least.
以及法律
And the law.
尤其是法律
Above all, the law.
吸血鬼有法律?
Vampires have laws?
不是很多
Not very many.
只有一條須強加執行
And only one that's regularly enforced.
是什麼?
What is it?
將我們的存在保密
That we keep the existence of our kind a secret.
絕不暴露人前
We don't make spectacles of ourselves,
也不在大庭廣眾下殺戮
and we don't kill conspicuously.
當然 除非你想死
Unless, of course, you want to die.
你能不說這事了嗎?
You gotta stop talking about that.
我不敢想像有人傷害你的情形
I can't even think about someone hurting you.
Bella 唯一能傷害我的只有你
Bella, the only thing that can hurt me is you.
除此之外我什麼也不怕
And I don't have anything else to be afraid of.
你說的不對
That's not true.
Victoria? 以後她會來找我的
Victoria? She'll come for me one day.
她決定了 Alice能預見 咱就能做好準備
Alice will see when she decides, and we'll be ready.
我可以保護你
I could protect you
如果你初擁了我
if you change me.
Bella 你已經在保護我了
Bella, you already do protect me.
你是我"活"下去的
You're my only reason
唯一理由
to stay alive,
可能我這樣算"活著"
if that's what I am.
但是我的職責是保護你
But it's my job to protect you.
不受任何人傷害 除了我妹妹
From everyone except my sister.
到點了! 到點了!
It's time! It's time. It's time. It's time!
* Your lips are nettles *
Your lips are nettles
* Your tongue is wine *
Your tongue is wine
* You're left as liquid But your body's pine *
You're left as liquid But your body's pine
很抱歉
Sorry about all this.
- 我們試著攔著Alice來著 - 說的好像你能做到似的
- We tried to rein Alice in. - As if that were even possible.
- 生日快樂 Bella - 謝謝
- Happy birthday, Bella. - Thanks.
我從你包包裡找到的 你介意嗎?
I found it in your bag. You mind?
泡比你大的妞 帥啊
Dating an older woman. Hot.
- 什麼? - 你先來 Rosalie
- What? - You first, Rosalie.
這是一個項鏈 Alice挑的
It's a necklace. Alice picked it out.
謝謝
Thanks.
恩愛一點看看
Show me the love.
這個是Emmett送的
This one's from Emmett.
已經安在你卡車上了
Already installed it in your truck.
終於有個像樣的音響了
Finally a decent sound system
- 那輛破的... - 嘿 別說我卡車的壞話
- for that piece of... - Hey! Don't hate the truck.
看看Esme和Carlisle的禮物
Open Esme and Carlisle's.
只是一些讓你開心的小禮物
Just a little something to brighten your day.
是啊 最近你看起來氣色不好
Yes, you've been looking kind of pale lately.
噢
Ow.
被紙割到了
Paper cut.
Jaz Jaz 沒事的 僅僅是一點
Jaz, Jaz. It's okay. It's just a little
血
blood.
帶Jasper出去
Get Jasper out of here.
對不起 我不行
I'm sorry, I can't.
得去我辦公室縫一下
I'll have to stitch this up in my office.
去看一下Jasper
Check on Jasper.
我肯定他現在肯定很內疚
I'm sure he's very upset with himself,
估計現在除了你 他誰的話也聽不進去
and I doubt he'll listen to anyone but you right now.
Edward
Edward.
- 我一直就沒想要開派對 - 這不是你的錯
- I never wanted to have a party. - It's not your fault.
Jasper斷人血的時間 不像我們這麼久
Jasper hasn't been away from human blood as long as the rest of us.
你怎麼做到的?
How do you do it?
年復一年的練習
Years and years of practice.
你有沒有想過簡單的那個方法?
Did you ever think of just doing it the easy way?
沒有
No.
我知道我想成為什麼樣的 我想要幫助人們
I knew who I wanted to be. I wanted to help people.
這樣讓我感到快樂 即使我無論如何都要被罰
It brings me happiness, even if I am damned regardless.
被罰?
Damned?
你指地獄?
Like hell?
Carlisle 你不會被罰下地獄的
Carlisle, you couldn't be damned.
你不會的 不可能
You couldn't. It's impossible.
謝謝你 Bella
Thank you, Bella.
你對我們一直很客氣
You've always been very gracious about us.
就是這個原因? 他就是因此不讓我變吸血鬼?
So that's it? That's why he won't change me?
換位思考一下
Imagine the situation in reverse. Hmm.
假如你和Edward想的一樣
If you believed as Edward does,
你會奪去他的靈魂嗎?
could you take away his soul?
你不能保護我
You can't protect me
不受任何傷害
from everything.
某一天 我們總會兩兩相隔
At some point, something's gonna separate us.
可能是事故或者疾病
It's gonna be an accident or illness
或者衰老
or old age,
只要我還是人類的話 唯一的解決辦法就是初擁了我
as long as I'm human. And the only solution is to change me.
那不是解決辦法 這叫悲劇
That's not a solution. That's a tragedy.
等我變成老奶奶時你就不會要我了
You're not gonna want me when I look like a grandmother.
Bella 你一點也不懂我對你的感覺嗎?
Bella, do you not understand my feelings for you at all?
Carlisle和我說了
Carlisle told me
你對自己靈魂的感覺
how you feel about your soul.
我不相信
I don't believe that.
所以也別擔心我
So don't worry about mine.
你該進屋了
You should go inside.
現在還是我的生日
It's still my birthday.
我能要求一件事嗎?
So can I ask one thing?
吻我?
Kiss me?
我愛你
I love you.
* Up with your turret *
Up with your turret
* Aren't we just terrified? *
Aren't we just terrified?
* Shale, screen your worry *
Shale, screen your worry
* From what you won't ever find *
From what you won't ever find
* Don't let it fool you *
Don't let it fool you
* Down *
Down
嘿
Hey.
跟我走走去
Just come take a walk with me.
我們要離開福克斯鎮了
We have to leave Forks.
為什麼?
Why?
Carlisle本該比他看起來老10歲
Carlisle's supposed to be 10 years older than he looks,
人們開始注意到了
and people are starting to notice.
好吧 我得編個理由和Charlie說
Okay, I've gotta think of something to say to Charlie.
你說"我們"...
When you say "we"...
我指的是我的家人和我
I mean my family and myself.
Edward Jasper的意外什麼也不是
Edward, what happened with Jasper, it's nothing.
你說的對 什麼也不是
You're right. It was nothing,
除了我一直預料的 什麼也不是
nothing but what I always expected
和可能發生的事相比 什麼也不是
and nothing compared to what could have happened.
你不屬於我的世界 Bella
You just don't belong in my world, Bella.
我屬於你
I belong with you.
不 你不屬於
No. You don't.
我來了
I'm coming.
Bella
Bella,
我不想你接近
I don't want you to come.
你不想要我?
You don't want me?
不想
No.
那樣的話一切都不同了
That changes things a lot.
恕我要求太多
But if it's not too much to ask,
你能答應我一件事嗎?
can you just promise me something?
不要魯莽行事
Don't do anything reckless.
為了Charlie
For Charlie's sake.
同樣我也答應你一件事作為回報
And I'll promise something to you in return.
這將是你最後一次見我
This is the last time you'll ever see me.
我不會再回來了
I won't come back,
你可以在沒有我的打擾下 繼續你的生活
and you can go on with your life without any interference from me.
就好像我從未存在過一樣 我保證
It will be like I never existed, I promise.
如果是因為我的靈魂 拿走吧 沒有你我也不想要啥靈魂了
If this is about my soul, take it. I don't want it without you.
和你的靈魂無關
It's not about your soul.
你只是不配我
You're just not good for me.
不配你是吧
Not good enough for you.
我很抱歉拖了這麼久
I'm just sorry I let this go on for so long.
求求你...
Please...
不要...
Don't...
再見
Goodbye.
Edward
Edward.
Edward!
Edward
Edward.
我要再打給Cullen家試試
I'm gonna try the Cullens' place again.
- Cullens家搬走了 Charlie - 可算滾蛋了
- The Cullens left town, Charlie. - Good riddance.
他們去哪了?
Where'd they go?
我們會找到她的 Charlie
We'll find her, Charlie.
- 謝謝 Harry - Charlie!
- Thanks, Harry. - Charlie!
嘿
Hey.
她沒事
She's all right.
我來吧 謝謝你 Sam
I got her. Thank you, Sam.
十月
* There's a possibility *
There's a possibility
十一月
* All that I had *
All that I had
* Was all I'm gonna get *
Was all I'm gonna get
Alice 你消失不見了
Alice, you've disappeared,
像其他一切
like everything else.
現在誰能聽我傾訴? 我很迷茫
Now who else can I talk to? I'm lost.
十二月
當你走時
When you left,
他也走了
and he left,
你帶走了一切
you took everything with you.
我只能看著他走後留下的空桌
But the absence of him is everywhere I look.
就像有人在我胸口重重打了一拳
It's like a huge hole has been punched through my chest.
Bella
Bella.
但我又有點開心
But in a way I'm glad.
唯有這疼痛提醒我 他是真的
The pain is my only reminder that he was real,
你們都是真的
that you all were.
好了 夠了
All right. That's it.
什麼?
What?
你回傑克遜維爾 和你媽一起住
You're going to Jacksonville to live with your mother.
我不要離開福克斯
I'm not leaving Forks.
Bells 他不會回來了
Bells, he's not coming back.
我知道
I know.
但這不正常 你的行為
It's just not normal, this behavior.
老實說 都快嚇死我和你媽了
Quite frankly, it's scaring the hell out of me and your mother.
寶貝 我也不想你走
Baby, I don't want you to leave.
我不想 但還是走吧 回到傑克遜維爾 交些新朋友
I don't, but just go. Go to Jacksonville. Make some new friends.
我喜歡我的老朋友
I like my old friends.
- 你都不見他們了 - 我有
- Well, you never see them anymore. - I do.
我明天和Jessica去逛街
I'm gonna go shopping tomorrow with Jessica.
- 你討厭逛街 - 我...
- You hate shopping. - I...
我要過個女生之夜
I need a girls' night out.
好吧 女生之夜
All right. Girls' night.
逛街
Shopping.
我喜歡 去買點東西也好
I like it. Go buy some stuff.
嗨 Jessica 是我Bella
Hi, Jessica, it's Bella.
是的 Bella Swan
Yeah, Bella Swan.
不明白你怎麼有耐性看完
I don't know why you want to sit through
那些殭屍吃人的場面 而不是看帥哥和美女親熱
all those zombies eating people and no hot guys kissing anybody.
很噁心不是嗎 像... 怎麼世上有這麼多殭屍電影呀?
It's gross. Like... And why are there that many zombie movies anyway?
感覺像是在學麻瘋病?
'Cause if it's supposed to, like, draw a parallel about leprosy,
我表弟有麻瘋病 這可一點都不好玩
my cousin had leprosy. It's not funny, you know?
算是暗喻用戶至上主義嗎?
And, like, is it supposed to be a metaphor for consumerism?
像是在說 不要滿足於自我...
Because don't be so pleased with your own, like,
自作聰明啥的
self-referential cleverness, you know?
就像 有些女孩喜歡逛街 但不是所有的女孩都喜歡
Like, some girls like to shop. Not all girls, apparently.
我還是很驚訝你會打電話約我
Although I was surprised you even called at all. You know?
你的失落 我明白 我真的 真的很擔心
Like, your depression thing, I get it. I'm totally, totally worried.
但過了一陣子後
But after a while it's like,
- 你還在鬱悶... - 要搭便車嘛 美女們?
- you're still bumming... - You want a ride, girls?
...我也有過心理波折 就像Mike決定
...and I'm going through stuff, too. You know? Like Mike deciding
他只想和我做朋友
he just wants to be friends.
看看我們找到了什麼?
What's up? Look what we found.
這很難
It's hard, you know?
啥時候開始流行"只做朋友"了...
Like, and since when does "just friends"...
- 夥計們 怎麼回事? - 看看我們的發現
- What's up guys? - Look what we found.
喔 喔 喔  嘿 你去哪裡?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, where you going?
繼續往前走
Keep walking.
這裡很危險
This is dangerous.
- 丫頭 回神 - 來一下下!
- Dude, come on. - Come here for a sec!
我想我認識他們
I think I know those guys.
我們有啤酒! 還有機車!
We got beer! We got bikes!
他們看著不錯 但我們能離開嗎?
Well, they seem great. Can we go?
我只想去看點東西
I'm just gonna see something.
嘿 美女們
Hey, girlie!
好了 好了 我們有乘客了
All right, all right. We got a taker.
轉身
Turn around.
- 閉嘴! - 你給我閉嘴!
- Shut up! - You shut up!
對不起 我把你當別人了
I'm sorry, I thought you were somebody else.
沒事 你想把我當誰都可以 寶貝
No, that's cool. I'll be whoever you want me to be, honey.
上來不?
So, what do you say?
你答應過 不會魯莽
You promised me, nothing reckless.
你也保證說 會像你從來沒存在過一樣
You promised it would be as if you never existed.
- 你撒謊 - 你說什麼 寶貝?
- You lied. - You say something, babe?
管他呢? 算了吧
You know what? Never mind.
停下! 停下 停下 快停下!
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
嘿 你發什麼神經?
Hey, what the hell's wrong with you?
只是有點好奇
Just curious.
- 我以為我看見什麼了 - 你... 噢
- I thought that I saw something. - You... Oh.
事實上 你瘋了 或者想自殺
You're insane, actually. Or suicidal.
那個老鄉可能是個神經病
That homeboy could've been a psycho.
我差點就要像蹩腳電視裡的那樣 走進FBI的訊問室了
I was about to end up in an FBI interview room like some lame TV show.
天哪 真刺激
God, that was such a rush.
好啊 你有腎上腺素癮癥啦?
Awesome. So you're an adrenaline junkie now?
行啊 那去蹦極好了
That's cool. You can go bungee jumping.
但不要去坐小混混的摩托車
You don't get on the back of some random loser's motorcycle.
瘋子
Crazy.
Alice 我看見他了
Alice, I saw him.
也許我瘋了 但沒關係
Maybe I'm crazy now. I guess that's okay.
如果只有遇險才能見到他
If a rush of danger is what it takes to see him,
我願意以身犯險
then that's what I'll find.
Bella!
你去哪裡了 瘋丫頭?
Where the hell have you been, loca?
我給你帶了點東西
I brought you something.
- 好吧 - 這玩意兒有點瘋狂
- Okay. - It's a little crazy.
喔哦
Wow.
破銅爛鐵 你真客氣
Scrap metal. You shouldn't have.
我從廢品站撿來的
I saved it from the junkyard.
我想修理價會比它的身價更高
I think they'll probably cost more to fix than they're worth,
然後我又想到 如果我有個懂機械的朋友
but then I thought that if I had a mechanic friend
- 願意幫我 那麼... - 啊!
- to help me out then... - Ah!
- 我就是那個懂機械的朋友? - 是的
- Me being the mechanic-type friend? - That's right.
- 你啥時候迷上摩托車了? - 現在開始
- Since when are you into motorcycles? - Since now.
如果你認為我很蠢很衝動 我理解
I get it if you think that this is really stupid and reckless.
是的哈 確實很愚蠢 很衝動
Yeah, I mean, it's completely stupid and reckless.
我們什麼時候開工?
When do we start?
呃
Um.
現在吧
Now.
- 求你了? - 好吧
- Please? - All right.
噢 嘿 小心點 這些傢伙很重的 所以...
Oh, hey, be careful. Those things are actually really heavy, so...
Jake 你真...健壯
Jake, you're, like, buff.
怎麼回事? 你不是才16歲嘛 我不明白
How did that happen? You're, like, 16. I don't get it.
呃... 年齡只是個數字 寶貝 你幾歲了呢? 40歲?
Mmm-hmm. Age is just a number, baby. What are you, like, 40 now?
我有時會有這種感覺
It feels like that sometimes.
那首歌很好聽 你不喜歡嗎?
That song's good. You don't like it?
我有點不再迷音樂了
I don't really like music anymore, kind of.
好吧 不聽音樂了
Okay. No more music.
我在想 如果我們每天都堅持動工
So I was thinking, if we're gonna do this every day,
但願我們每天都能開工
and hopefully we will,
我們是否要 在哪裡先做點功課
we have to, like, fit some homework in there somewhere.
我不想讓Billy覺得我把你帶壞了
I don't want Billy thinking that I'm a bad influence on you.
你? 帶壞我? 拜託
You? Influence me? Please.
你...我年紀比你大
Are you... I'm older than you,
所以我就是施影響者 而你則是受影響的人
so that makes me the influencer and you the influencee.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我的個頭和知識庫 都比你大
My size and knowledge base actually makes me older than you
因為你整日蒼白 又不諳世事
because of your general paleness and lack of know-how.
我好歹說服你 跟我一起修理2輛報廢機車
I convinced you to build two-wheeled death machines with me.
這沒讓你覺得自己幼稚天真嗎?
Don't you think that makes you kind of young and naive?
好吧 那咱多大?
Okay. So where do we stand?
- 我35歲了 你估計也就32吧 - 少來
- I'm 35. And you might be, like, 32. - Come on.
- 喲 Jake 在家嗎? - 沒事 是我哥們
- Yo, Jake, you in there? - It's okay. It's just my boys.
- 嘿 Jake - 嘿 夥計們 這位是Bella
- Hey, Jake. - Hey. Guys, this is Bella.
- Bella 這兩位是Quil和Embry - 嗨
- Bella, that's Quil and Embry. - Hi.
我叫Quil Ateara
I'm Quil Ateara.
這麼說還真有修機車這事
So the bike building story is true.
噢 是的 沒錯 我手把手教會他
Oh, yeah, yeah, I taught him everything he knows.
那麼你是他女朋友這話可是當真?
What about the part where you're his girlfriend?
呃...
Uh...
我們是朋友
We're friends, you know.
- 糗大了 - 實際上
- Burn. - Actually,
記得我是這麼說的 她是女性-朋友
remember I said she's a girl and a friend.
Embry 有記得他這麼區分嗎?
Embry, do you remember him making that distinction?
沒有
Nope.
你們都有女朋友? 很贊哇
So you guys have girlfriends? That's awesome.
嗯 是的 Quil帶他表妹去參加畢業舞會
Yeah, right. Quil's actually taking his cousin to prom.
是啊 也算轟動嘛
Yeah, that's still a riot.
想搞笑嘛 Black? 那我讓你爽一下
You want funny, Black? I'll give you funny.
見鬼
Jeez.
嘿 這麼抱算著犯規!
Hey, that hold's illegal!
我壓5塊錢賭Quil贏
I got five bucks on Quil.
賭就賭
You're on.
* All of the astronauts Champagne in plastic cups *
All of the astronauts Champagne in plastic cups
* Waiting for the big hero to show *
Waiting for the big hero to show
* Outside the door he stands His head in his hands *
Outside the door he stands His head in his hands
* And his heart in his throat *
And his heart in his throat
*What can he tell them now*
What can he tell them now
親愛的Alice
Dear Alice,
真希望能有你的真實地址
I wish I had your real address.
真希望能跟你講講Jake
I wish I could tell you about Jake.
他讓我的好過很多
He makes me feel better.
他讓我感覺生機勃勃
I mean, he makes me feel alive.
我胸口的傷痛
The hole in my chest,
和Jake在一起時 好像痊癒了
well, when I'm with Jake, it's like it's almost healed
有那麼一陣子
for a while.
Quil一直說要來這裡 我想他有點喜歡你過頭了
So, Quil keeps asking to come over. I think he likes you a little too much.
噢
Oh.
我對姐弟戀可沒興趣 懂不?
Well, I'm really not into the whole cougar thing. You know?
你和你年紀較啥勁呢?
What's up with you and age?
Cullen那傢伙又幾歲了?
I mean, how old was that Cullen guy, anyway?
但 即使Jake也沒辦法趕走夢魘
But even Jake can't keep the dreams away.
嘿 嘿 嘿!
Hey, hey, hey!
醒醒 Bella
Wake up, Bella.
你沒事 你沒事
You're okay. You're okay.
我還以為這玩意兒有用 看樣子沒用
I thought this thing was starting to work, but I guess not.
能問你點事嗎?
Can I ask you something?
和Jacob一起玩
Hanging out with Jacob,
好像有點轉移你的注意力 不是嗎?
that seems to take your mind off things a bit, doesn't it?
有時候
You know, sometimes
你得學會去愛對自己有益的事物
you gotta learn to love what's good for you.
懂我的意思嗎?
You know what I mean?
當然 我知道個啥呢?
Of course, what do I know?
我只不過是個終極單身漢
I'm just a terminal bachelor.
出了名得有女人緣
Famous ladies' man.
好了
Okay.
我去睡覺了
I'm gonna go to bed.
呃...
Uh...
我愛你
I love you.
如果我說 我沒法修好摩托車 你會說什麼?
If I told you I couldn't have fixed these bikes, what would you have said?
你在懷疑自己的瘋狂技能?
Are you doubting your mad skills?
不 當然不是 它們能跑起來
No. Definitely not. I mean, they'll run fine.
只是
It's just,
如果我夠聰明 我應該放慢維修速度
maybe if I was smart, I would have dragged out the rebuild a bit.
如果你說你不能修好摩托車 我會說 真糟糕
If you told me you couldn't fix these bikes, I would say that that's really too bad,
那我們只能去找別的事做了
but that we're just gonna have to find something else to do.
那個是Sam Uley嗎?
Is that Sam Uley?
是的 他和他的信徒
Yeah. Him and his cult.
噢 天哪
Oh, my God.
你看到了嗎?
Did you see that?
他們不是真打架 Bella 他們在玩懸崖跳水
They're not really fighting, Bella. They're cliff diving.
非常恐怖 但是很刺激
Scary as hell, but a total rush.
- 刺激? - 大部分人都選擇矮的地方跳
- A rush? - Most of us jump from lower down.
就讓Sam和他的門徒顯擺好了
We leave the showing off to Sam and his disciples.
你跟他有啥過節?
You have some kind of beef with him or something?
我不知道
I don't know.
他們覺得自己擁有這個地方
They just think they run this place.
Embry以前稱他們為 打了類固醇的糾察隊員
Embry used to call them hall monitors on steroids.
- 瞧他現在這樣子 - 那個是Embry?
- Now look at him. - That's Embry?
- 是的 - 他怎麼回事?
- Yeah. - What happened to him?
他翹了幾天課
He missed some school.
突然之間 他開始做Sam的跟屁蟲
Now all of a sudden, he started following Sam around like a little puppy.
Paul和Jared也這樣
Same thing happened with Paul and Jared.
Sam不停地用怪異的眼神看我
Sam keeps giving me this look,
好像他在等我或什麼的
like he's waiting for me or something.
我覺得有點恐怖
It's kind of starting to freak me out.
你還是躲著他比較好
Well, you should just avoid him.
我在努力
I try.
好了
Okay.
- 你好像很怕 - 我不怕
- You look scared. - I'm not.
好吧
All right.
- 剎車? - 那個
- Brake? - That one.
離合器?
Clutch?
很好
Good.
汽油?
Gas?
準備好了嗎?
Ready?
慢慢鬆開離合器
Now, slowly release the clutch.
Bella
Bella.
停下
Stop.
你沒事吧?
You all right?
我再試一次
I'm gonna go again.
好的
Okay.
踩剎車!
Hit the brake!
我要再來一次
I wanna go again.
你想自殺嗎?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
- 不 我要再試一次 - 不 想都別想
- No. I want to go again. - No. Forget it.
不准再騎機車
No more bikes.
噢 你的額頭
Man, your head.
- 是的 - 噢 天哪 對不起
- Yeah. - Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
什麼 你為自己流血而道歉?
What, you're apologizing for bleeding?
我想是的
Yeah. I guess I am.
只流了一點血 Bella 不嚴重
Well, it's just blood, Bella. No big deal.
來
There.
你盯啥呢?
What are you staring at?
你長得還挺帥
You're sort of beautiful.
你腦子被撞傻了?
How hard did you hit your head?
我不知道
I don't know.
我們走吧
Let's go.
我確實在樹林裡看見過
I did see something in the woods.
寶貝 我相信你
Totally. Baby, I believe you.
不 他不信 他只想撞運罷了
No, he doesn't. He's just trying to get lucky.
沒有 那玩意烏黑烏黑的 非常大
No, okay. It was jet black and huge.
四腳觸地 還比人要高
On all fours, it was still taller than a person.
可能是熊?
A bear, maybe?
或者是外星人 你沒被針戳算你走運
Or an alien. You're lucky you didn't get probed.
我看見它了
Well, I saw it.
不只你看見過
You know, you're not the only one.
我爸爸在警局接到舉報
My dad's been getting reports at the station.
5個背包客被啥熊殺害
Like, five hikers have been killed by some bear.
但卻一直找不到那只熊
But they can't find the bear.
呃
Hmm.
這是你們丫最後一次敢懷疑我女朋友
Last time you clowns doubt my girlfriend.
呃...
Um...
那麼...
So? I mean,
Bella回來了?
Bella's back?
我想是的
Yeah, I guess so.
很好 這個...  歡迎你
All right, that's... Well, welcome.
聽著 既然你又開始說話
So, listen, now that you're talking
吃飯 你好歹得補點蛋白質
and eating again, which, you know, you've got to get that protein in there,
不知...你要不要和我一起去看電影
I was just wondering if you wanted to go see a movie with me.
嗯 當然了 是的 我願意
Yeah. Sure. Yeah, I do.
很好
Cool.
我們可以去看
Let me see, we could check out
"終究是愛"
Love Spelled Backwards Is Love.
片名有點俗 但是部浪漫喜劇
You know, it's a dumb title, but it's a romantic comedy.
- 應該會蠻... - 不 不要浪漫的
- I mean, it's supposed to be pretty... - No. No romance.
"一擊即中"怎麼樣? 聽說過這部電影嗎?
How about Face Punch? Have you heard of that?
是部動作片
I mean, that's an action movie.
嗯 很完美
Yeah, that's perfect.
槍械 腎上腺素
Guns, adrenaline.
是我的茶
That's my thing.
好吧
Okay.
我們應該多叫幾個人一起 你們想去看"一擊即中"嗎?
We should get a bunch of people to go. Do you guys want to go see Face Punch?
"一擊即中" 耶!
Face Punch, yeah!
Mike 嘿 我們說要去看的
Mike, hey, we were supposed to watch that.
還記得嘛 那個預告片...
Remember, the trailer's like...
- 超火爆的 - 我記得
- "Punch faces." - I remember.
耶! 和Bella共度電影之夜
Yeah! Movie night with Bella.
"一擊即中"哈?
So Face Punch, huh?
你喜歡動作片?
You like action movies?
不是很喜歡
Not really.
聽說不好看 很爛
I heard it sucks. Bad.
你夠年紀看這電影?
Are you even old enough to see this movie?
沒有成人監督下可以嗎?
I mean, you know, without, like, adult supervision.
噢 她在幫我買票
Right, yeah, well, she's buying my ticket for me.
她在買 好的
She's buying it. Okay.
Jessica耍約 Angela得了腸胃炎
Jessica bailed, and Angela got the stomach flu,
Eric在照顧她
so Eric's taking care of her.
- 只有我們仨 - 很好!
- It's just us three. - Great!
- 很好 - 是的
- Great. - Yeah.
把槍放下
Put your gun down.
你把槍放下 否則我就打爆你的腦袋
Put your gun down or I'm gonna blow your frickin' head off.
你們倆都把槍放下
Both of you put both of your guns down
否則我就打爆你們倆的腦袋
or I'm gonna blow both of your frickin' heads off.
好吧 算了 我們開戰吧!
All right, forget it, let's do this!
我想我要吐了
Okay, I think I'm gonna throw up.
他...
He's...
真是脆弱啊!
What a marshmallow!
你得找個腸胃堅強點的人
You should hold out for someone with a stronger stomach.
嘲笑讓懦弱男人嘔吐的血腥場面的人
Someone who laughs at the gore that makes weaker men vomit.
好的 我會留意的
Yeah. I'll keep my eye open for that.
我好內疚哦 他可能得了流感了
I feel bad. He probably has that flu that's going around.
怎麼了 我不能牽你的手嗎?
What? I can't hold your hand?
能 你當然能
No, of course you can.
我只是認為這動作對你來說有特殊含義 所以...
I just think it means, you know, something a little different to you. So...
好吧 說出來吧 你喜歡我 對吧?
Okay, well, tell me something. You like me, right?
而且你覺得我挺帥的?
And you think I'm sort of beautiful?
Jacob 拜託 不要這樣
Jacob, please, don't do this.
為什麼?
Why?
因為你會毀了這一切的
Because you're about to ruin everything.
而且我需要你
And I need you.
我有大把的時間
Well, I've got loads of time.
我不會放棄的
I'm not gonna give up.
我也不想你放棄
I don't want you to,
但那只因我不想你離開
but it's just 'cause I don't want you to go anywhere.
這真是自私啊
And that's really selfish.
我不像一輛能被你修好的汽車
You know, I'm not like a car that you can fix up.
我再也不會正常行駛了 所以我對你該公平些
I'm never gonna run right. So I should be fair to you.
都是因為他 是不是?
It's because of him, right?
聽著
Look,
我知道他對你做了什麼
I know what he did to you.
但是Bella 我永遠也不會那樣做的
But, Bella, I would never ever do that.
我永遠也不會傷害你 我發誓
I won't ever hurt you. I promise.
我不會令你失望的
I won't let you down.
你能依靠我
You can count on me.
好了
Well,
我得回家了
I need to go home.
電影前我就覺得想吐了
I was feeling sick before the movie. Okay?
你啥毛病吶?
What is your problem?
現在嗎? 就是你
Right now? You're my problem.
想吐? 或許你應該去醫院了
Feeling sick? Maybe you need to go to the hospital.
想讓我把你送進醫院嗎
You want me to put you in the hospital?
Jake 電影都放完了 你這是在幹什麼?
Jake! Jake. Jake, the movie's over. What are you doing?
你身上真熱
You're really hot.
好像發燒了似的 你還好嗎
Like, you feel like you have a fever. Are you okay?
我不知道怎麼了
I don't know what's happening.
我得走了
I gotta go.
那傢伙太奇怪了
That dude is weird.
Jake 你爸說你得了單細胞核增多癥
Jake, your dad says you have mono.
他不讓我來看你 你能回個電話嗎
He won't let me visit, but would you call me?
嘿 還是我 我只是...
Hey, it's me again. I just...
對於在電影院說過的話我很抱歉
I'm sorry about what I said at the movie theater.
我只是想聽聽你的聲音 別緊張
I just wanted to hear your voice, so no pressure.
Jacob 拜託
Jacob, please...
給我打電話
Call me.
我們大概三點回來
Okay. We should be back around 3:00.
嘿
Hey.
我今天不是非去釣魚不可
Look, I don't have to go fishing today.
你得去
Yes, you do.
是的 你要去 走吧 還在說什麼
Yeah, you do. Go. What are you talking about?
注意安全
Just be careful.
向來如此
Always am.
那些熊打不過我的 Bella
Those bears won't get the drop on me, Bella.
我功夫很厲害的
My kung fu is strong.
Jake
Jake!
嘿
Hey!
你剪了頭髮?
You cut your hair off?
做了紋身?
And got a tattoo?
Bella
Bella.
我以為你病的出不了門呢
I thought you were too sick to come outside
或者接不動我電話吶
or pick up the phone when I call.
走開
Go away.
什麼?
What?
走開
Go away.
你怎麼了 什麼事兒
What happened to you? What's...
嘿 發生什麼了
Hey! What happened?
Sam找你了 就是這事兒嗎?
Did Sam get to you? Is that what's happening?
Sam想幫我 不要怪他
Sam's trying to help me. Don't blame him.
如果你想怪誰
But if you want somebody to blame,
你深愛的那些個骯髒的吸血鬼怎麼樣 Cullen一家?
how about those filthy bloodsuckers you love, the Cullens?
我不懂你在說什麼
I don't know what you're talking about.
不 你知道的清清楚楚
No, you know exactly what I'm talking about.
你向每個人都撒了謊 Charlie
You've been lying to everyone. Charlie.
但是你不能欺騙我
But you can't lie to me.
- 再也不能了 Bella - Jacob!
- Not anymore, Bella. - Jacob!
Jacob!
聽著 Bella
Look, Bella,
我們不能再做朋友了
we can't be friends anymore.
Jake 我知道我傷害了你
Look, Jake, I know that I've been hurting you.
我備受折磨 像死一樣難過
It's killing me. It kills me.
我只是需要...給我點
I just need... Maybe give me, like,
- 時間或什麼的 - 不用了
- some time or something. - Look, don't.
不是因為你
It's not you.
不怪你 是我 對嗎?
It's not you, it's me, right? Really?
是真的 因為我
It's true. It is me.
我不夠好
I'm not good.
我曾經是個乖孩子的
I used to be a good kid.
再也不是了
Not anymore.
這一點兒也不重要 行嗎
This doesn't even matter. All right?
全結束了
This is over.
你不能和我分手
You can't break up with me.
我是說...
I mean...
你是我最好的朋友啊
I mean, you're my best friend.
你保證過的
You promised me.
我知道
I know.
我保證過不會傷害你 Bella
I promised I wouldn't hurt you, Bella.
我正在堅守我的誓言
And this is me keeping that promise.
回家吧
Go home
不要回來 不然你會受傷的
and don't come back or you're gonna get hurt.
Alice
Alice,
一切都...
things are...
又變的糟糕了
Things are bad again.
沒有了Jake 我...我堅持不下去了
Without Jake, I just... I can't stand it.
我再沒見到Edward了
I don't see Edward anymore.
真能做到像他從未存在過一般麼?
Will it really feel like he never existed?
我會找到能見到他的地方
I will find the place where I can see him again.
Bella
Bella.
Laurent
Laurent.
沒想到在這兒能見到你
I didn't expect to find you here.
我去拜訪Cullen一家 但房子空了
I went to visit the Cullens, but the house is empty.
我真驚訝他們把你留下了
I'm surprised they left you behind.
你不就如
Weren't you sort of
他們的個寵物嗎?
a pet of theirs?
是 可以這麼說吧
Yeah. You could say that.
Cullen一家經常看你嗎?
Do the Cullens visit often?
撒謊
Lie.
是的 當然 一直有來
Yeah, absolutely, all the time.
編好點
Lie better.
我會告訴他們你來過的
I'll tell them that you stopped by.
或許我不應該
But I probably shouldn't
告訴Edward
tell Edward,
因為他太保護我了
'cause he's pretty protective.
但是他遠在天邊 不是嗎
But he's far away, isn't he?
你為什麼來這?
Why are you here?
算是幫Victoria一個忙
I came as a favor to Victoria.
- Victoria? - 她讓我來看看
- Victoria? - She asked me to see
你是不是還在Cullen庇護之下
if you were still under the protection of the Cullens.
鑒於Edward殺了她的伴侶
Victoria feels it's only fair to kill Edward's mate,
Victoria覺得只有殺了他的才夠公平
given he killed hers.
以牙還牙
An eye for an eye.
威脅他
Threaten him.
Edward會知道是誰幹的 他會找你算賬的
Edward would know who did it. And he'd come after you.
我不這麼認為
I don't think he will.
畢竟 他把你毫無庇護地丟在這兒
After all, how much could you mean to him
你對他能算是什麼?
if he left you here unprotected?
我殺了你Victoria會不高興的
Victoria won't be happy about my killing you,
但我忍不住
but I can't help myself.
你太令人垂涎欲滴了
You are so mouth-watering.
- 求你不要 你幫過我們的 - 不不不
- Please, don't. I mean, you helped us. - No, no, no, no.
別害怕 我這是在幫你
Don't be afraid. I'm doing you a kindness.
Victoria打算慢慢折磨死你
Victoria plans on killing you slowly,
痛苦地
painfully,
但是我會很快了結你
whereas I'll make it quick.
我保證
I promise.
你什麼都感覺不到
You will feel nothing.
Edward 我愛你
Edward, I love you.
我不相信
I don't believe it.
- 爸 我看見它們了 - 怎麼了?
- Dad! I saw them. - What's the matter?
- 在樹林裡 不是熊 - 在樹林裡 什麼意思?
- In the woods. They're not bears. - What do you mean "in the woods"?
Bell 你去樹林裡幹什麼
Bell, what the hell were you doing out in the woods?
它們是狼 巨型的狼
They're wolves. I mean, they're like huge wolves.
你確信 Bella?
Are you sure about that, Bella?
是的 我剛剛看見它們 它們在追趕著什麼
Yeah! I just saw them. They were after something.
狼?
Wolves?
你看見它們了?
You saw them?
好吧 Harry
All right, well, Harry,
想打獵麼 把你的夥計們聚起來?
feel like going hunting? Get some of your guys together?
當然 只是...
Sure, yeah, I'll just...
眼下那些狼該沒命了
By now, those wolves will be dead,
Laurent會告訴她我毫無保護
and Laurent would have told her I'm unprotected.
Victoria
Victoria.
我要去局裡
I should go to the station.
是的 你應該去
Yeah, you should. You should go.
你能待在屋裡嗎?
Can you just stay in the house?
Bella
Bella!
你嚇著我了
You scared me.
- 你到底在幹什麼? - 後退 我要上來了
- What the hell are you doing? - Back up. I'm coming up.
嘿
Hey.
聽著 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
- 為什麼? - 真希望我能解釋
- For what? - I wish I could explain.
但我真不能說
But I literally can't.
你有過不能告訴任何人的秘密嗎?
Have you ever had a secret you couldn't tell anyone,
不能與他人分享的秘密?
one that wasn't yours to share?
我就是這樣
Well, that's what it's like for me.
但更糟糕
But worse.
你不知道我被拘束得多緊
You have no idea how tight I'm bound.
我討厭這樣
I hate this.
我恨他們對你做的
I hate what they've done to you.
我是說 吸血鬼的那部分 你已經知道了
I mean, the killer part is, you already know.
Bella 你記得我們在拉普什海灘上散步嗎?
Bella, do you remember when we walked on the beach at La Push?
那個...
The...
那個關於
The story. The story about
吸血鬼的故事
the cold ones.
我已經知道為什麼你只記得那部分了
I guess I understand why that's the only part you remember.
一定有些什麼你能做的
There's gotta be something that you can do.
不 我生來如此
No. I'm in it for life.
或許我們應該離開一陣子
Well, maybe we should just get out of here for a while.
只管離開
Just leave,
只有你和我
just you and me.
你願意這樣?
You'd do that?
為了你 我會的
I would do it for you.
這不是我能一逃了之的事情 Bella
It's not something I can just run away from, Bella.
但如果可以
But I would run away with you
我會和你一起逃開
if I could.
我要走了 他們會起疑我去哪兒了
I gotta go. They'll start wondering where I am.
過來
Come here.
請你
Please,
試著記住
try to remember.
如果你知道一切
It'd be so much easier
你會好受很多
if you knew.
我會的 但是Jake...
I'll try. But, Jake...
Jake 你在幹什麼 等等 Jake
Jake, what are you doing? Wait, Jake.
Jake
Jake.
Edward 我很害怕
Edward, I'm scared.
你應當如此
You should be.
這只是個古老傳說了
Really, it's just like an old story.
我真的應該什麼也不說的
I'm not really supposed to say anything about it.
你知道Quileute族是狼的後代嗎?
Did you know Quileutes are supposedly descended from wolves?
Bella
Bella?
我要見他
I need to see him.
他不在
He's not in.
- 我很抱歉 我真的需要見見他 - Bella
- Okay, I'm sorry, I really need to see him. - Bella!
你們做什麼了
What did you do?
- 你們都做了什麼? - 嘿
- Okay, what did you do? - Hey.
- 你們對他怎麼樣了? - 放鬆
- What did you do to him? - Easy!
他不想這樣
He didn't want this.
我們做什麼了 他呢 他告訴你什麼了?
What did we do? What did he do? What'd he tell you?
- 你們都冷靜點兒 - 什麼也沒有
- Both of you calm down. - Nothing.
他什麼也沒告訴我 因為他害怕你們
He tells me nothing because he's scared of you.
- 太遲了 - Bella 回去
- Too late now. - Bella, get back!
Paul 冷靜下來 現在
Paul, calm down, now!
Bella
Bella!
快跑
Run!
Jake 快跑
Jake, run!
Paul
Paul!
嘿 把Bella帶回Emily那兒
Hey! Take Bella back to Emily's place.
看起來狼的秘密暴露了
Guess the wolf's out of the bag.
Alice 這一切有可能是真的嗎?
Alice, is it possible that everything is true?
童話和恐怖故事
The fairy tales and horror stories?
是否可能理智與正常根本不存在?
Is it possible that there isn't anything sane or normal at all?
嘿 我覺得該回去看看Jacob是不是安好了
Hey, I think we should go back and see if Jacob's okay.
我希望Paul用牙咬他 他是罪有應得
I hope Paul sinks some teeth in him. Serves him right.
沒可能 Jacob是天才
No way. Jacob's a natural.
你看他跑時的樣子沒? 我打包票Paul根本碰不到他
You see him phase on the fly? I got five says Paul doesn't touch him.
進來 Bella 我們不會咬你的
Come on in, Bella. We won't bite.
說你自己呢吧
Speak for yourself.
* I done me wrong *
I done me wrong
* And done all wrong *
And done all wrong
* All the wrong I've done I'm sure I'll live quite long *
All the wrong I've done I'm sure I'll live quite long
嘿 Emily Sam的未婚妻 別盯著看 Sam最討厭那樣
Oh, hey, about Emily, Sam's fiance? Don't stare. It bugs Sam.
我為什麼要盯著
Why would I stare?
夥計們餓了沒 真是明知故問
Are you guys hungry? Like I have to ask.
這位是
Who's this?
Bella Swan 還能有誰
Bella Swan. Who else?
嗯
Hmm.
那麼 你是吸血鬼的女友
So, you're the vampire girl.
那麼 你是狼人的女友
So, you're the wolf girl.
算是
Guess so.
我都和個狼人訂婚了
Well, I'm engaged to one.
給你兄弟留點兒吧 女士優先 要鬆餅嗎?
Save some for your brothers. And ladies first. Muffin?
當然 謝謝
Sure. Thanks.
讓Jacob自己想辦法琢磨Sam的禁言令吧
Leave it to Jacob to find a way around Sam's gag order.
他什麼也沒對我說
He didn't say anything to me.
那是狼族的事兒
That's a wolf thing.
老大的命令要無條件服從
Alpha's orders get obeyed whether we want them to or not.
知道嗎 我們能讀懂彼此的想法
And check it out. We can hear each other's thoughts.
能閉嘴麼 這些可是秘密 丫的!
Would you shut up? These are trade secrets. Damn it!
這小妞和吸血鬼一路的
This chick runs with vampires.
我可跟不上他們的腳步
You can't really run with vampires.
他們太快了
'Cause they're fast.
真的麼 我們速度更快
Yeah? Well, we're faster.
嚇到了沒?
Freaked out yet?
你不是我見到的第一個怪物了
You're not the first monsters I've met.
Jake說對了 你很能接受奇怪事物
Jake's right. You're good with weird.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉
Sorry.
那麼 你是狼人?
So you're a werewolf?
是的 千真萬確
Yeah. Last time I checked.
部落裡一小部分幸運兒有這個基因
A few lucky members of the tribe have the gene.
吸血鬼搬進城了 我就全身發燒
A bloodsucker moves into town and the fever sets in.
單核細胞增多癥
Mono.
我倒希望是
Yeah. I wish.
你們找不到方法停止嗎?
Well, can't you find a way to just stop?
我的意思是 這不對
I mean, it's wrong.
這可不是選擇生活方式 Bella
It's not a lifestyle choice, Bella.
天生的 我也管不住
I was born this way. I can't help it.
你真虛偽 怎麼 我不是你要的那款怪物?
You're such a hypocrite. What, I'm not the right kind of monster for you?
這無關你是什麼種族
It's not what you are.
是你做了什麼 他們從未傷害任何人
It's what you do. They never hurt anybody.
你們殺人了 Jake
You've killed people, Jake.
Bella 我們沒殺過任何人
Bella, we're not killing anyone.
那是誰幹的?
Then who is?
我們試圖保護你們人類免受他們傷害的
What we're trying to protect you people from,
那些我們唯一殺的
the only thing we do kill,
吸血鬼
vampires.
等下 Jake 你不能
Wait, Jake, you can't.
別擔心 我們不會動你的寶貝Cullen一家
Don't worry. We can't touch your little precious Cullens
除非他們違反契約
unless they violate the treaty.
我不是這個意思
That's not what I'm saying.
你們不能殺吸血鬼 他們會...
You can't kill vampires. They'II...
他們會殺了你的
They'll kill you.
真的嗎 我們把那個吸血鬼輕易了結了
Really? We took out that leech with the dreads easy enough.
Laurent?
他的紅髮女友是下一位
And his red-headed girlfriend is next.
Victoria在這兒?
Victoria's here?
曾經在 那晚我們一路追蹤她到加拿大邊境
Was. We chased her all the way to the Canadian border the other night.
她總回來 我們不知道她要找什麼
She keeps coming back. We don't know what she's after.
我知道
I do.
我
Me.
別擔心 我們嚴守這一塊兒
Don't worry. We've got this place covered.
她不會接近你和Charlie的
She won't get near you or Charlie.
你小心點
Look, you've got to be careful.
她速度很快 遠遠超越你的想像
She's fast. You don't know how fast she is.
你對我們沒信心 有點侮辱人哦
You know, your lack of confidence in us is a little insulting.
好吧 我得走了
All right, I'd better go.
你要走嗎?
You gotta go?
是
Yeah.
去獵殺吸血鬼
Got a vampire to kill.
Alice 我沒事
Alice, I'm all right.
除了有些孤單
Until I'm alone.
最近始終如此
And lately, that's all the time.
Jacob走了 他去獵殺Victoria
Jacob's gone. He's hunting Victoria.
而Charlie在獵殺Jacob
And Charlie's hunting Jacob.
你又走了
And you're gone.
Edward也走了
And so is Edward.
於是現在空無一片
And there's just nothing now.
你有發現嗎 Harry?
You got something, Harry?
沒 沒有
Nope. Nothing.
但我知道我該去哪裡
But I realize where I have to go,
我必須做什麼才能再次見他
what I have to do to see him again.
* A tear in my brain *
A tear in my brain
* Allows the voices in *
Allows the voices in
* They wanna push you off the path *
They wanna push you off the path
* With their frequency wires *
With their frequency wires
* And you can do no wrong *
And you can do no wrong
* In my eyes *
In my eyes
* You can do no wrong *
You can do no wrong
* In my eyes *
In my eyes
* A drunken salesman *
A drunken salesman
* Your hearing damage *
Your hearing damage
* Your mind is restless *
Your mind is restless
* They say you're getting better *
They say you're getting better
* But you don't feel any better *
But you don't feel any better
* Your speakers are blowing *
Your speakers are blowing
* Your ears are wrecking *
Your ears are wrecking
* Your hearing damage *
Your hearing damage
* You wish you felt better *
You wish you felt better
* You can do no wrong *
You can do no wrong
* In my eyes *
In my eyes
別這麼做
Don't do this.
你想讓我做人類
You wanted me to be human.
看著我
Watch me.
求你
Please.
為了我
For me.
除此辦法之外 你我不能廝守
You won't stay with me any other way.
Bella 求你
Bella, please.
* This constant noise all the time *
This constant noise all the time
* Even though you're the only one I see *
Even though you're the only one I see
呼吸!
Breathe!
醒醒!
求你了 Bella 醒醒!
Come on, Bella, breathe!
Bella Bella 能聽到我嗎?
Bella? Bella, can you hear me?
Jake?
過來
Come here.
你想什麼呢你?
What the hell were you thinking?
我只是想看一些東西
I just wanted to see something.
送她回家! 我去幫Harry的忙
Get her home! I'm gonna go help out over at Harry's place.
Harry怎麼了?
What happened at Harry's?
據說Harry心臟病發作
Harry Clearwater had a heart attack.
Charlie和我爸去慰問他的家人了
Charlie and my dad are over at his place with his family.
他還好嗎?
Is he okay?
他過世了
He's gone.
來 我幫你弄乾然後送你回家
Come on. I'll get you something dry and drive you home.
我身上熱的很吶
108 degrees over here.
老天!
God!
我的手凍僵了
My hands are freezing.
永不會冷的感覺一定很棒
It must be nice, never getting cold.
狼人都會如此
It's a wolf thing.
不
It's not.
只有Jacob這樣
It's a Jacob thing.
你真的很溫暖
You're just warm.
你就像太陽一樣
You're like your own sun.
這樣更好 現在你瞭解我了
This is better, now that you know about me.
但...
But...
你看到Emily的事了吧
You saw what happened to Emily.
Sam怒了
Sam got angry.
只是一秒鐘的失控
Lost it for a split second.
而Em當時站得太近
Em was standing too close.
他永遠無法挽回了
He'll never be able to take that back.
如果我對你怒了該如何?
What if I got mad at you?
有時
Sometimes,
我感覺自己快要消失
I feel like I'm gonna disappear.
並不是說 你需要我
Okay, not that you need me
對你說這樣的話
to tell you something like this,
但我會一直提醒你 你不會迷失自己
but I always will. You're not gonna lose yourself.
我不會讓那種事發生的
I wouldn't let that happen.
怎麼做?
How?
我會一直對你說
I'll tell you all the time
你是多麼與眾不同
how special you are.
謝謝 為我所做的一切
Thank you. For everything.
等等
Wait.
這裡有個吸血鬼
There's a vampire.
你怎麼知道?
How do you know?
我可以聞到 我帶你離開這
I can smell it. I'm getting you out of here.
那是Carlisle的車
That's Carlisle's car.
他們在這裡
They're here.
Bella 是個圈套 停! 你跟我走!
Bella, it's a trick! Stop! You gotta come with me!
他們不會傷害我的
They won't hurt me.
如果Cullen一家回來  這裡是他們的領地
If a Cullen is back here, this is their territory.
契約規定我們只保衛自己的領地
Treaty says we can only defend on our own lands.
- 在這裡我不能保護你 - 好的 沒事 不必
- I can't protect you here. - Okay. That's okay. You don't have to.
你好像打算越界
You're about to cross a line.
那就別劃界線
Then don't draw one.
求你?
Please?
Alice?
- 哦 老天! 你怎麼... - Bella!
- Oh, my God! What are you... - Bella!
抱歉 我只是 我只是無法相信你會在這兒 你...
I'm sorry, I just, I can't believe you're here. Is...
能給我解釋一下你怎麼活下來的嗎?
Would you like to explain to me how you're alive?
什麼?
What?
我在幻象中看到你跳崖
I saw a vision of you. You jumped off a cliff.
你究竟為何要自殺?
Why in the hell would you try and kill yourself?
Charlie怎麼辦?
I mean, what about Charlie?
- 怎麼辦... - 我不是嘗試自殺
- What about... - I didn't try to kill myself.
我是要跳崖
I was cliff jumping.
鬧著玩的!
Recreationally.
有趣而已
It was fun.
我從沒見過如此不顧性命的蠢行
I have never met anyone more prone to life-threatening idiocy.
你...
Does...
你告訴他了嗎?
Did you tell him?
沒
No.
他只是每幾個月來一個電話
He only calls in once every few months.
他說他想獨處
He said he wants to be alone.
Bella 為什麼聞起來 會有可怖的落湯狗的味道?
Bella, what is that God-awful wet dog smell?
嗯...
Um...
可能是我
That's probably me.
或者Jacob的氣味
Or it's Jacob.
Jacob是誰?
Jacob who?
Jacob是狼人
Jacob's kind of a werewolf.
Bella!  狼人可不是什麼志趣相投的夥伴
Bella! Werewolves are not good company to keep.
說你自己呢吧
Speak for yourself.
我來看看你是否安全
I had to see you were safe.
我記得你說在這你不能保護我
I thought you couldn't protect me here.
也許我不在意這些了
Guess I don't care.
我不會傷害她的
Well, I'm not gonna hurt her.
是 你是一個無害的Cullen家的人
No, you're just a harmless Cullen.
我說的是另外一個吸血鬼 因為你們而想殺了Bella
I'm talking about the other bloodsucker who tried to kill Bella because of you.
Victoria?
是的 Victoria曾在附近出現
Yeah, Victoria's been around.
我沒看見過她
I didn't see her.
我也沒看見有人把你從水裡救出
I didn't see you get pulled out of the water, either.
我看不見你和你們那群瘋狗
I can't see past you and your pack of mutts.
別惹我...
Don't get me upset...
- 嘿 停 停 停 停 - ...否則給你難堪
- Hey, stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop. ...or things are gonna get very ugly.
我給你們點時間
I'll give you a minute.
嗨
Hey.
別去其他地方 到時回這來
You're not going anywhere. You're gonna come back,
- 對嗎? - 你一趕走這隻狗我就回來
- right? - As soon as you put the dog out.
他...
Is he...
還有其他Cullen家的人在嗎?
Are there others? How many Cullens are here
他們要待多久?
and how long are they staying?
沒
No.
只有Alice一個
It's just Alice.
她隨便待多久都可
And she can stay as long as she'd like.
那其他人會回來嗎?
Well, are the rest coming back?
不
No.
據我所知不會
Not that I know of.
還有別的事嗎?
Anything else?
就這些
That's it.
如果沒事 那你最好趕快回Sam那裡
Well, if that's all, then you'd better go run back to Sam.
我又這麼做了
I've done it again.
不斷違背我的誓言
I keep breaking my promise.
我們之間不必如此
We don't have to do this to each other.
不 需要
Yes, we do.
Bella...
這裡是Swan家
Swan residence.
他現在不在
He's not here right now.
他安排葬禮去了
He's arranging a funeral.
哪位?
Who was that?
怎麼了?
What?
總是擋道
Always in the way.
是誰?
Who was that?
Bella 退後
Bella, step back.
- Jake 是誰? - Bella! Bella 是Edward
- Jake, who was that? - Bella! Bella, it's Edward.
他以為你死了 Rosalie告訴了他我來這的原因
He thinks you're dead. Rosalie told him why I came here.
你為什麼...不讓我跟他說話?
Why would you... Why didn't you let me speak to him?
- 他沒有找你 - Bella
- He didn't ask for you. - Bella.
- 我不在乎! - Bella Bella 他要去找Volturi家族
- I don't care! - Bella. Bella! He's going to the Volturi.
他也想死
He wants to die, too.
他拋棄了你 Bella 他不再要你 記得嗎?
JACOB: He left you, Bella. He didn't want you anymore. Remember?
不 我不能讓他因為內疚而去送死
No, I'm not gonna let him kill himself out of guilt.
那你爸爸怎麼辦?
What about your dad?
我18歲了 從法律上講我行動自由 而我也留了紙條
I'm 18. I'm legally free to go, and I left a note.
求你 Bella
Please, Bella,
留下
just stay here.
為Charlie
For Charlie.
或為我
Or for me.
我必須去
I have to go.
我求你
I'm begging you.
求你
Please.
再見 Jacob
Goodbye, Jacob.
好吧
Okay.
你打定主意了哈
So you've made up your minds.
我有點可惜你的天賦
I'm afraid your particular gifts
如此珍貴不應毀滅
are too valuable to destroy.
如果你惋嘆命運不幸 可加入我們
But if you're unhappy with your lot, join us.
我們也樂意利用你的的能力
We would be delighted to utilize your skills.
你何不考慮下留在我們這裡嗎?
Won't you consider staying with us?
你明知早晚會如此
You know it will happen anyway.
但不會毫無由頭
Not without cause.
暴殄天物!
Such a waste.
我猜這輛你不是租來的吧?
I'm guessing you didn't rent this car?
我想你眼下不會介意我偷車
I figured you wouldn't be opposed to grand theft auto.
今天不會
Not today.
怎麼了? 你看到什麼了?
What? What do you see?
他們拒絕了他
They refused him.
- 那? - 他想暴露身份
- So? - He's gonna make a scene.
- 把自己的身份暴露給人類 - 不! 什麼時候?
- Show himself to the humans. - No! When?
他會等到正午 太陽升到最高點
He's gonna wait until noon, when the sun's at its highest.
天呢 Alice 你開快點
God, Alice, you got to hurry up.
那就是沃特拉
There's Volterra.
- 為何他們都身著紅裝? - 慶祝聖馬庫斯節
- Why are they all in red? - San Marco's Day festival.
紀念吸血鬼被逐出這個城市
They're commemorating the expulsion of vampires from the city.
背景很完美
It's the perfect setting.
在此暴露 Volturi家族絕不會放過他
The Volturi will never let him get far enough to reveal himself.
我們只有5分鐘
We have five minutes.
我知道 Bella 深呼吸
I know, Bella, just breathe.
Alice!
Bella 你是唯一一個他不會想到會來的人
Bella, you're the only one he can't see coming.
換成我 他會讀我思維 他會因為我的欺騙而選擇速死
If I go, he'll read my thoughts. He'll think I'm lying. He'll rush into it.
- 我去哪找? - 他就在鍾塔下面 快!
- Where do I go? - He'll be under the clock tower. Go!
別!
Don't!
這是天堂
Heaven.
必須進去
You have to move.
睜開眼睛 看看我 我還活著
Open your eyes. Look at me. I'm alive.
必須進去
You have to move.
Bella
Bella.
- 你來了 - 是我
- You're here. - I'm here.
你還活著
You're alive.
對
Yes.
我想讓你再次看到我
I needed to make you see me once.
必須讓你知道我還活著
You had to know that I was alive,
這樣你就不必內疚
that you didn't have to feel guilty about anything.
現在我可以讓你走了
I can let you go now.
我絕不是因為內疚
I never acted out of guilt.
沒有你我活不下去
I just couldn't live in a world where you don't exist.
- 但你說... - 我騙你的
- But you said... - I lied.
我必須撒謊 但你卻那麼輕易就信了
I had to lie. But you believed me so easily.
因為你愛我 這說不通啊
Because it doesn't make sense for you to love me.
我一無是處 我是人類 無關緊要
I mean, I'm nothing. I'm human. I'm nothing.
Bella 你於我是一切
Bella, you're everything to me.
全部
You're everything.
我現在不需要你們的幫忙了 紳士們
I won't be needing your services after all, gentlemen.
Aro想再次跟你聊聊
Aro wants to speak with you again.
沒有破壞規矩
No rules were broken.
雖說如此 咱應該到個更適合的審判地談吧
Nonetheless, we should take this conversation to a more appropriate venue.
好吧
Fine.
Bella 要不你和大家一起歡度節日?
Bella, why don't you go and enjoy the rest of the festival?
這女孩必須跟我們一起走
The girl comes with us.
不 你去死吧
No. You can go to hell.
別逗了 夥計們
Come on, guys.
這是慶祝節日 你們也不願引起騷動
It's a festival. You wouldn't want to make a scene.
我們不想
We wouldn't.
夠了
Enough.
Jane
Jane.
Aro派我來看下為何要這麼久
Aro sent me to see what was taking so long.
按她吩咐的意思做
Just do as she says.
你們先請
Go ahead.
別害怕
Don't be scared.
你呢?
Are you?
不
No.
- 她是人類? - 是
- Is she human? - Yes.
她知道這一切?
Does she know?
是
Yes.
那為何...
Then, why would...
想要成為...
She wants to be.
她會轉變的
And so she will be.
或者成為甜點
Or dessert.
妹妹 讓你抓一個你卻帶回來兩個
Sister. They send you out to get one and you bring back two.
還有半個
And a half.
真是個聰明姑娘
Such a clever girl.
真是個驚喜!
What a happy surprise!
Bella終究還是活著吶
Bella is alive after all.
簡直棒極了哈?
Isn't that wonderful?
我喜歡圓滿的結局
I love a happy ending.
啊
Ah.
罕見啊
They are so rare.
她甜美的鮮血如此吸引你
Her blood appeals to you so much
都讓我飢渴了
it makes me thirsty.
你距她一步之遙何以忍住?
How can you stand to be so close to her?
- 並不容易 - 是 我可以理解
- It's not without difficulty. - Yes, I can see that.
Aro只要輕輕一摸 就可以知道我所有的想法
Aro can read every thought I've ever had with one touch.
現在你知曉一切了
And now you know everything.
那就繼續吧
So get on with it.
你的讀心術也很不錯啊 Edward
You are quite a soul reader yourself, Edward.
儘管如此你卻無法獲悉Bella的想法
Though you can't read Bella's thoughts.
妙啊!
Fascinating.
我很願意看看你是否也能防禦我的能力
I would love to see if you are an exception to my gifts, as well.
肯賞光嗎?
Would you do me the honor?
有趣
Interesting.
嗯
Hmm.
我什麼都沒有讀到
I see nothing.
我非常好奇...
I wonder if...
讓咱看看她是否對我們所有的能力都免疫
Let us see if she's immune to all our powers.
能展示下嗎 Jane?
Shall we, Jane?
- 不! - 疼痛
- No! - Pain.
住手!
Stop!
住手! 求你! 住手!
Stop! Please! Stop!
住手! 別傷害她! 求你! 求你!
Stop! Just stop hurting him! Please! Please!
Jane?
主人?
Master?
繼續 親愛的
Go ahead, my dear.
這可能會有些痛
This may hurt just a little.
太不可思議!
Remarkable!
她挫敗了我們所有人
She confounds us all.
那我們現在該如何處置你呢?
So what do we do with you now?
你已知道怎麼做 Aro
You already know what you're going to do, Aro.
她知道的太多了
She knows too much.
她是個負擔
She's a liability.
嗯
Hmm.
的確如此
That's true.
Felix?
不!
No!
求你! 不! 不! 求你! 求你!
Please! No! No! Please, please!
殺了我! 殺了我! 別傷害他
Kill me! Kill me! Not him.
多特別啊!
How extraordinary.
你竟然願意為我們這類放棄生命
You would give up your life for someone like us.
為吸血鬼
A vampire.
一群無魂的怪物
A soulless monster.
放她走!
Just get away from her!
你對他的靈魂一無所知
You don't know a thing about his soul.
真是悲劇!
This is a sadness.
只要你有意使她永生
If only it were your intention to give her immortality.
等等!
Wait!
Bella會成為我們的一員
Bella will be one of us.
我預見到了
I've seen it.
我來初擁她
I'll change her myself.
令人著迷!
Mesmerizing.
能遇見尚未發生之事
To see what you have seen before it has happened.
你的天賦將成就一個有趣
Your gifts will make for an intriguing
而不朽的
immortal,
Isabella
Isabella.
去吧
Go now.
做好準備
Make your preparations.
我們來親自來處理
Let us be done with this.
Heidi隨時會到
Heidi will arrive any moment.
感謝你們的拜訪
Thank you for your visit.
我們也會熱情回饋
We will return the favor.
我建議你們立即實現諾言
I would advise that you follow through on your promise soon.
下不為例
We do not offer second chances.
再見 我的年輕朋友們
Goodbye, my young friends.
收穫不錯 Heidi
Nice fishing, Heidi.
是 他們的確看來誘人
Yes, they do look rather juicy.
給我留點
Save some for me.
走這邊 一起走
This way, please. Stay together.
停! 停!
Stop! Stop!
你還在
You're here.
安心睡吧
You can sleep.
你睡醒前我都會守著你
I'll still be here when you wake up.
Bella 我離開你的唯一原因
Bella, the only reason I left
是我以為我是在保護你
was because I thought I was protecting you.
我希望你
I needed you
有機會過上正常快樂的生活
to have a chance at a normal, happy life.
你可以那麼輕易的離開我
It was so easy for you to leave.
離開你是我這一百年最艱難的事
Leaving you was the hardest thing I've done in 100 years.
我發誓
And I swear,
我不會再辜負你
I will never fail you again.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
- Charlie來了 - 嗨
- Charlie's coming. - Hey.
你還好嗎?
You okay?
還好
I'm fine.
爸 你不必擔心我
Dad, you don't have to worry.
上次你這樣說 你出走了
You know, last time you said that, you took off.
三天都不見
I didn't see you for three days.
我真的很抱歉 爸爸
I'm really sorry, Dad.
Bella 別再這麼對我
Bella, do not ever do that to me again.
永遠別
Ever.
你被禁足了哦
And you're grounded
終生禁足哦
for the rest of your life.
好吧
Okay.
嚴格說 我沒有違反他的規定
I'm not technically breaking any of his rules.
他的確有說 我不能踏進門內一步
He did say I couldn't take a step inside the door.
我是從窗子進來
I came in through the window.
他不會這麼容易原諒我的
He's not gonna forgive me easily.
我知道
I know.
你呢?
Can you?
我希望你能
I hope you can,
因為沒有你 我真的不知如何生活
'cause I honestly don't know how to live without you.
過來
Come here.
一旦Alice把我轉變
Once Alice changes me,
你就別想再拋棄我
you can't get rid of me.
她不一定要轉變你
She won't need to change you.
一定還有別的方法可以瞞住Volturi家族
There are always ways to keep the Volturi in the dark.
不 不
No. No.
你們都知道我想要的
You all know what I want.
而我也知道我的要求有些過分
And I know how much I'm asking for.
我認為唯一公平的是大家投票表決
The only thing that I can think of for it to be fair is to just vote.
- 你不知道你在說什麼 - 閉嘴
- You don't know what you're talking about. - Shut up.
Alice?
我已經把你當成我的姐妹了
I already consider you my sister.
- 我同意 - 謝謝
- Yes. - Thank you.
我也投"同意"
JASPER: I vote "yes."
這樣我就不用一直想要殺你
It would be nice to not want to kill you all the time.
嗯
Hmm.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我為之前的行為向你兩道歉
I'm really sorry to both of you for how I've acted,
而且我真感激的是你足夠勇敢
and I'm really grateful that you were brave enough
去救我弟弟
to go and save my brother.
但換了我 我不會選擇這樣的生活
But this isn't a life I would have chosen for myself.
如果是我 我希望有人能阻止我
And I wish that there'd been someone to vote "no" for me.
故此 我反對
So, no.
我當然投"同意"
I vote "Hell, yeah."
我們用別的方法打擊Volturi家族
And we can pick a fight with these Volturi some other way.
我早把你當成是家庭的一員了
I already consider you a part of the family.
我同意
Yes.
你為什麼要這樣對我?
Why are you doing this to me?
你知道裡邊的含義
You know what this means.
你選擇沒她不活 這讓我別無選擇
You've chosen not to live without her, which leaves me no choice.
我不想失去我的兒子
I won't lose my son.
我想等到畢業以後再做 這樣子Charlie會好過些
I'll wait until after graduation to make it easier on Charlie.
Edward 我希望由你親自來做
Edward, I want you to be the one to do it.
他想和我聊會
He wants to talk to me.
因此你現在還活著
So you're still alive for now.
他認為是我把你帶遠了
He thinks it's me keeping you away.
別讀我的想法
You stay the hell out of my head.
Jacob 我知道你有話對我說
Jacob, I know you have something to say to me.
如果可以的話 我想先對你說點什麼
But I want to say something to you first, if that's all right.
謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝你在我不在的時候保護Bella
Thank you for keeping Bella alive when I didn't.
不 你確實不在
No. You didn't.
我不是為你保護她 相信我
And it wasn't for your benefit, trust me.
我還是很感激
I'm still grateful.
但現在我回來了
But I'm here now.
除非她趕我走否則我不會離開她
I'm not gonna leave her side until she orders me away.
咱們走著瞧
We'll see.
該我說了
Hey, my turn to talk.
我提醒你別忘記我們契約的一個重點
I'm here to remind you about a key point in the treaty.
我沒忘
I haven't forgotten.
什麼重點?
What key point?
如果你們中任何人咬了人類
If any of them bites a human,
停戰就會結束
the truce is over.
但如果我是自願 就不關你事
But if I choose it, it has nothing to do with you.
不 不 我不會讓你
No. No, I won't let you.
你不能變成他們的一份子 Bella
You're not gonna be one of them, Bella.
這你不能決定
It's not up to you.
你知道我們會怎樣對你 我別無選擇
You know what we'll do to you. I won't have a choice.
Bella 拜託 走吧
Bella, please, come.
等等
Wait.
他會傷害我嗎? 讀他的想法
Is he gonna hurt me? Read his mind.
Jake
Jake,
我愛你
I love you.
所以 求你
So, please,
不要逼我抉擇
don't make me choose,
因為我一定選他
'cause it'll be him.
一直就是他
It's always been him.
Bella...
- 再見 Jacob - 不 不用你為她說
- Goodbye, Jacob. - No, you don't speak for her!
Bella 咱們走
Bella, get out of here.
停!
Stop!
你們互相傷害 我也不能倖免
You can't hurt each other without hurting me.
Jake
Jake.
他是對的
He's right.
你不該變成我這樣
You shouldn't become what I am.
我一個人做不到
I can't do this alone.
那就請等等
Then, please, just wait.
給我五年的時間
Just give me five years.
這太長了
That's too long.
那麼三年?
Then three?
你真固執
You're so stubborn.
你要等什麼?
What are you waiting for?
我有一個條件
I have one condition
如果你要我親自來的話
if you want me to do it myself.
什麼條件?
What's the condition?
約束永遠
And then forever.
正如我願
That's what I'm asking.
嫁給我 Bella
Marry me, Bella.
新月 -=結束=-
White demon love song down the hall
White demon shadow on the road
Back up your mind, there is a call
He isn't coming after all
Love this time
She likes the way he sings
White demon love song's in her dreams
White demon, where's your selfish kiss?
White demon sorrow will arrange
Let's not forget about the fear
Black invitation to this place that cannot change
While strangely holy
Come for a rain
White demon, widen your heart's scope
White demon, who let your friend go?
- Let us be in love - Let us be in love
- Let's do old and gray - Let's do old and gray
- I won't make you cry - I won't make you cry
- I will never stray - I will never stray
- I will do my part - I will do my part
Let us be in love tonight
White demon, widen your heart's scope
White demon, who let your friend go?
Stand it anymore, darling
Stand it
Meet me on the equinox
Meet me halfway
When the sun is perched at its highest peak
In the middle of the day
Let me give my love to you
Let me take your hand
As we walk in the dimming light
Oh, darling, understand
That everything, everything ends
Meet me on your best behavior
Meet me at your worst
For there will be no stone unturned
Or bubble left to burst
Let me lay beside you, darling
Let me be your man
And let our bodies intertwine
But always understand
That everything, everything ends
That everything, everything, everything ends
A window
An opened tomb
The sun crawls
Across your bedroom
A halo
A waiting room
Your last breaths
Moving through you
As everything, everything ends
As everything, everything, everything
Everything, everything, everything ends
Meet me on the equinox
Meet me halfway
When the sun is perched at its highest peak
In the middle of the day
Let me give my love to you
Let me take your hand
And as we walk in the dimming light
Oh, darling, understand
That everything, everything ends